const STORE = [
    {
      number: 1,
      question: 'In the TV show “fresh off the boat” which character is actually the writer of the original novel?',
      answers: [
        'Eddie Huang',
        'Emery Huang',
        'Evan Huang',
        'Louis Huang'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Eddie Huang',
    },
    {
      number: 2,
      question: 'In “fresh off the boat” what was Grandma Huang’s English name?',
      answers: [
        'Jenna',
        'Jessica',
        'Jenny',
        'Jen'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Jenny',
    },
    {
      number: 3,
      question: 'In season 1 where did Huang family move from? ',
      answers: [
        'Orlando, FL',
        'Hong Kong',
        'Washington D.C',
        'Taiwan'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Washington D.C',
    },
    {
      number: 4,
      question: 'In Season 1 what exam did Jessica passed?',
      answers: [
        'Realtor',
        'Insurance',
        'Certified Public Accountant (CPA)',
        'Nursing test'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Realtor',
    },
    {
      number: 5,
      question: 'In Season 2 whose concert was held in Orlando on Valentine’s Day?',
      answers: [
        'Jay Z',
        'Janet Jackson',
        'Dr.Dre',
        'Michael Jackson'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Janet Jackson',
    },
    {
      number: 6,
      question: 'In Season 2 what was Jessica’s favorite TV show?',
      answers: [
        'Beverly Hills',
        'Baywatch',
        'Melrose Place',
        'Pacific Palisades'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Melrose Place',
    },
    {
     number: 7,
      question: 'In Season 3 when Huang family flew to Taiwan,Jessica bought a pair of knock off shoes in the night market. What brand was it?',
      answers: [
      'Adidas',
      'Nike',
      'Gucci',
      'Converse'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Nike',
    },
    {
      number: 8,
      question: 'In Season 3 which movie did Louis and Gary go to watch together? ',
      answers: [
        'Hamlet',
        '10 things I hate about you',
        'Shakespeare in Love',
        'Romeo + Juliet'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Romeo + Juliet',
    },
    {
     number: 9,
      question: 'In Season 4 which celebrity’s death made Honey extremely upset?',
      answers: [
      'Mother Teresa',
      'Princess Diana',
      'Amy Whitehouse',
      'Michael Jackson'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Princess Diana',
    },
    {
      number: 10,
      question: 'In Season 4 which celebrity was used as an example of hardworking by Jessica?',
      answers: [
        'Lucy Liu',
        'Michelle Kwan',
        'Tiger Woods',
        'Jackie Chan'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Michelle Kwan',
    }
];
